[Music]
thank you
it is a beautiful morning the
wildflowers are dancing in the wind and
looking quite pleased with themselves
I'm enjoying a long walk with my husband
watching as storm clouds mix with a
gentle Sun
[Music]
the weather has been changeable lately
as we all are I think we can be sure
that in our own lives Sunshine will be
followed with periods of rain and vice
versa I think that is one of my favorite
things about being alive that everything
is impermanent and changeable
during hard times I take comfort in
knowing things will change during good
times I know I must appreciate the
moment because I have known the rain
I even appreciate death because I think
it gives meaning to life and I've come
to appreciate a lot of things that we
sometimes fear or find uncomfortable and
see the beauty in it
[Music]
thank you
most scary things are not quite so when
taken out into the light I feel the same
in regards to myself there's nothing to
dislike or fear in me not when I really
look at it what I dislike is only pain
wishing to be soothed with love and what
I fear is only a call to grow and find
my courage
foreign
[Music]
with my sister one day telling her about
a small personal challenge I was trying
to overcome and I said I was so
frustrated that I can't just change
myself at the snap of my fingers I can't
just immediately be who I want to be I
know I should love myself but why can't
I simply love why is it so hard to apply
what I've learned sometimes her response
resounded with me she said Paola let's
say you snap your fingers and you're
suddenly exactly who you want to be
you've grown and matured in all the ways
you need to you are perfect what then
what is the point of your life where do
you go from here will you even be proud
of that person
I kept thinking of that long after I
finished talking to her as it felt
deeply true there is no thing that
brings me Greater Joy than going through
the process of learning from life and
celebrating my achievements along the
way from then onward I wanted to accept
that the process of becoming your best
self takes a lifetime there isn't any
point in negative self-criticism if I've
accepted that my journey is about making
mistakes and learning from them
[Music]
thank you
becoming an observer of your own choices
actions relationship Dynamics and even
emotions is an incredible tool in
becoming your best friend because you
see yourself as just that a friend a
someone you must take care of and
support as well as challenge now you may
think that that's obvious being
self-aware is just that I'm serving
yourself and reflecting but we often do
so much in our lives where we don't
apply that sense of reflection we say
things we don't mean or are unkind to
ourselves and others without wondering
why we do that and what does that tell
us about ourselves how can this
awareness help us practice humility
which I will always believe is the
starting point to all great change for
the better
when I look at myself through humble
eyes I see why constant criticism isn't
humble at all because it is as if you
expect yourself to be perfect when it's
impossible
this has helped me change the way I talk
to myself and slowly ever so slowly
become my best friend
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
I don't know if you can actually hear me
it is
not too windy but there are so many bugs
and birds out and about I'm not sure if
I'm going to be audible at all but since
this is one of my favorite places I
decided that I would give it a try
are you going to join us
I I had to readjust the camera a little
bit due to my dog breathing very loudly
into the microphone so here we are
hopefully you can hear me at least a bit
I had a bit of a hard week to be honest
I kind of overloaded myself with stuff
to do and that is something I tend to do
in the springtime
because it is finally warm I have all
this you know Newfound excitement for
the spring and this new season and I
don't always know how to reel myself
back in
and so I felt myself feeling a little
bit overwhelmed and I did not like the
headspace I was in due to not feeling
super great I decided to come out here
to another one of my favorite little
spots around my home this is only about
a mile or so away from where I live and
it is worth the walk I love the bright
purple of the lupins and the Larkspur
mixed together over here and the smell
of the Lupine is so distinct and it
never fails to calm me down whenever I
do make videos about being overwhelmed
I do find it interesting that quite a
few people always comment that I don't
seem overwhelmed at all and I thought
I'd use that as a great example for a
lot of people you know you don't really
know what they're feeling on the inside
and you can't always tell on the outside
I am someone that likes to keep those
things quite private and there's
actually a downside to that because I
think that it makes it more difficult
for me to let others know when I need a
bit of a break and so it's been quite
important to me as I grow older to grow
into a more assertive person and someone
who's more clear with what they need and
their boundaries which I know can be
really hard for a lot of people to do
one technique when I'm feeling off in
any way it doesn't matter the emotion
usually
is to find a lovely place to sit you
obviously do not need a field of flowers
you know a peaceful corner of your room
is just fine and using that opportunity
to observe your feelings instead of
being them it's thinking about it more
like I have feelings that are rather sad
or feelings that are overwhelming and
you are not those feelings you are not
defined by how you feel and those
feelings are not who you are you are so
much more than that you can over time
learn to observe your feelings so that
they do not quite have the same weight
over you but that can be hard to do it's
a very very long process I'm still on
that process sometimes just sitting and
and practicing that separating myself
from how I feel re-labeling how I feel
instead of saying oh I'm so upset I
can't stand it instead being these uh
feelings are rather uncomfortable right
now but they're very manageable it will
be okay and relabeling those things and
transforming my experience helps me so
much
yeah
I should probably wrap this up oh I
probably need to get home I did hear
that there were storms on the forecast
but I did not realize they were going to
be coming so soon well I hope you
enjoyed this beautiful Loop and field
with me it means so much to share it
with you for anyone interested always
down below I share links to some charity
and Conservancy groups that mean a lot
to me if you have enjoyed these videos
if you love nature if you love
preserving wildlands do check out those
links or find your own ways to
contribute because this field is too
beautiful and I want places like this to
last forever
and so I appreciate you humoring me and
hearing me out and I hope you have a
wonderful wonderful week and I'm gonna
head home before I get rained on or
lightning or something worse so
sending so much love goodbye
[Music]